hey loves sh Beauty sent me this let's
unbox to see what's
inside we have here a welcome card and a
$10 gift
card this leaflet here contains all you
need to know about the brand the product
and their ingredients this is the chbe
hair butter its key ingredients are CH
powder cocoa butter sh butter etc etc
the texture is very
smooth next is the chi shampoo with its
ingredients as CH powder aloe vera
lavender the CH deep conditioner is made
from CH powder coconut oil djoba oil and
tea tree oil rice water as it name
implies is made from fermented rice
water and other ingredients the rosemary
oil is made from Cher powder and other
oils additionally I was gifted hair
kits these wear hair bands hair clips
large hair clips Bobby pains and hair
straps isn't this
lovely thank you so much sh Beauty for
this product I can't wait to use it and
share my honest review about
them and thank you too for watching bye